flyerspecials.com 2017-12-13

# Flyers Specials Saving Weekly Grocery Store Ads Flyer ads

** Private Privacy**

 **Private Privacy**

* * *

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we assure you that personal information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in contacting flyerspecials.com for access to personal information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

Flyerspecials.com may on occasion combine information we receive from you to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive online marketing information from this or any other one of our sites please notify us by email : [Privacy@flyerspecials.com](mailto:Privacy@flyerspecials)

Finally, flyerspecials.com will not use or disclose personal information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above.

**Cookies**  
To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files that maybe placed in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

Flyerspecials.com uses reputable third parties to serve the advertisements that you see on our Web site. In the course of serving advertisements, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser and may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you..

**Our Commitment to Security**  
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the personal information we collect.
